# COREY FERLAND

# WEB DEVELOPER I SOFTWARE ENGINEER

BEDFORD, NY (339) 788-1820 FERLANDC@GMAIL.COM

GITHUB.COM/CFERLAND LINKEDIN.COM/IN/COREY-FERLAND

### **SUMMARY**

I am a highly motivated Software Engineer with a background in Client Services and social media. I bring a broader understanding of design and marketing which allows me to seamlessly integrate user experience concepts into the applications I develop. Driven by creating top-notch customer experiences, I strive to exceed both internal and external expectations in the products I create and the services I provide.

## **SKILLS**

Customer Service, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node, Python, SQL, Ruby, CLI, GitHub, UI Development, Agile Methodology, JSON, API Usage, Wordpress, SEO, Google Analytics

## **EXPERIENCE**

# General Assembly — Jr. Web Developer, Software Engineering Immersive

NOVEMBER 2019 - PRESENT | NEW YORK, NY

- Developed full stack applications with React and other technologies.
- Collaborated with UX Design team to convert hi-fidelity prototypes into full-stack website for local NYC restaurant.
- Implemented mobile-friendly and responsive functionality to various projects.
- Utilized version control through Git and the command line.

### Whole Foods Market — Customer Success

FEBRUARY 2013 - NOVEMBER 2019 | VARIOUS LOCATIONS

- Created policies and managed client-facing staff to ensure delivery of exceptional customer service
- Managed relationships and catering operations for enterprise clients
- On-boarded and trained 100+ employees across various Whole Foods locations
- Problem-solved various equipment and software issues as needed

# Child Care Resource — IT & Social Media Intern

SEPTEMBER 2011 - MAY 2012 | WILLISTON, VT

- Updated and managed website content using HTML & CMS.
- Researched and utilized SEO strategies to increase web presence.
- Monitored social media accounts and analyzed reach data.

### **EDUCATION**

General Assembly — Software Engineering Immersive

NEW YORK, NY

University of Massachusetts — B.S. Natural Resource Conservation

AMHERST, MA

South Shore Technical School — Graphic Communications

HANOVER, MA